♪I don't want to be free♪
♪ لا أريد أن أكون حراً ♪
=I Don't Want To Fall in Love with Human=
= لا أريد الوقوع في حب الإنسان =
Ms. Lu, are you planning to give birth?
السيدة لو ، هل تخططين للولادة؟
After giving it a thought,
بعد التفكير فيه ،
looking at your age,
بالنظر إلى عمرك ،
you should do it quickly.
يجب عليك القيام بذلك بسرعة.
You should be able to give birth to five children for His Highness.
يجب أن تكون قادرًا على إنجاب خمسة أطفال لسموه.
Although I'm totally against the idea of the woman older than her husband,
على الرغم من أنني ضد فكرة أن تكون المرأة أكبر سناً من زوجها ،
I can't help it
لا يسعني ذلك
since the pearl is with you.
لأن اللؤلؤة معك.
Uncle Hai, giving birth is women's right,
العم هاي الولادة حق للمرأة
not women's job.
ليس عمل المرأة.
However, giving birth for mermaids
ومع ذلك ، ولادة حوريات البحر
is your responsibility and duty.
هي مسؤوليتك وواجبك.
Uncle Hai, I care not about
العم هاي ، لا يهمني
mermaids and I don't want to.
أنا وحوريات البحر لا أريد ذلك.
I just want to take out the pearl
أنا فقط أريد أن أخرج اللؤلؤة
for you to leave immediately.
لتغادر على الفور.
His Highness is seeing this kind of woman.
سموه يرى هذا النوع من النساء.
It's life-threatening.
إنها تهدد الحياة.
Why are you standing here?
لماذا انت واقف هنا؟
Do you think Qing Bu Liang is delicious?
هل تعتقد أن تشينغ بو ليانغ لذيذ؟
Ask your fiancee.
اسأل خطيبتك.
What?
ماذا؟
What attitude is that?
ما هو هذا الموقف؟
I'll get it myself.
سأحصل عليه بنفسي.
(Sea pearl)
(لؤلؤة البحر)
Ms. Bai!
السيدة باي!
Why did you come in without knocking on the door?
لماذا أتيت دون أن تطرق الباب؟
I got a notice today that
لقد تلقيت إشعارًا اليوم بذلك
I was fired.
لقد تم فصلي.
The acquisition project is over.
انتهى مشروع الاستحواذ.
You don't have to stay.
ليس عليك البقاء.
Over? Why is it over?
على؟  لماذا انتهى؟
Over 70 shops have signed the agreement.
وقع أكثر من 70 متجرا على الاتفاقية.
Only Xiangyu left.
غادر Xiangyu فقط.
Give me 10 more days.
أعطني 10 أيام أخرى.
No, five days. Give me five more days.
لا ، خمسة أيام.  أعطني خمسة أيام أخرى.
I'll get Xiangyu to sign the agreement.
سأجعل Xiangyu يوقع الاتفاقية.
Sunset Beach's acquisition project is over.
انتهى مشروع الاستحواذ على Sunset Beach.
I have other arrangement.
لدي ترتيب آخر.
I bet all my hopes in
أراهن بكل آمالي
Sunset Beach's acquisition project.
مشروع الاستحواذ على شاطئ الغروب.
If you end it now, I'll lose everything.
إذا أنهيت الأمر الآن ، فسوف أفقد كل شيء.
Song Nan, you're fired.
سونغ نان ، أنت مطرود.
Bai Qing, you'll regret this.
باي تشينغ ، سوف تندم على هذا.
Get out!
اخرج!
Zeyi, you went and bought Qing Bu Liang?
Zeyi ، ذهبت واشتريت Qing Bu Liang؟
This is yours.
هذا لك.
Zeyi,
زي ،
Qing Bu Liang is my favourite.
تشينغ بو ليانغ هو المفضل لدي.
This is yours.
هذا لك.
Zeyi, this is my favourite garage kit.
زيي ، هذا هو طقم المرآب المفضل لدي.
Zeyi.
زي.
Miaomiao, I think it's done.
Miaomiao ، أعتقد أنه انتهى.
Drink it.
اشربه.
Help me.
ساعدني.
What's wrong with her?
ما هو الخطأ معها؟
Maybe she failed to make a new drink,
ربما فشلت في صنع مشروب جديد ،
so she felt bad.
لذلك شعرت بالسوء.
Zeyi, try it.
زيي ، جربه.
So sour.
تعكر جدا.
She will make a loss.
سوف تخسر.
Come on, Your Highnesses.
تعال يا أصحاب السمو.
Let's try the coconut bar that Momo made.
لنجرب لوح جوز الهند الذي صنعه مومو.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Of course. Momo
بالطبع.  مومو
is the woman I chose for Zeyi.
هي المرأة التي اخترتها لزيي.
She's gentle, cute, kind, and she can give birth.
إنها لطيفة ولطيفة ولطيفة ويمكنها أن تلد.
It's a shame that someone cut the queue.
من العار أن يقوم شخص ما بقطع قائمة الانتظار.
Actually, Miaomiao is not bad.
في الواقع ، Miaomiao ليس سيئًا.
Come on. She's fierce and old.
هيا.  إنها شرسة وكبيرة في السن.
You need to look for a wife
أنت بحاجة للبحث عن زوجة
who is gentle and loyal.
من هو لطيف ومخلص.
Lu Miaomiao is not that kind of woman.
لو مياومياو ليس هذا النوع من النساء.
Uncle Hai, let me repeat myself.
عمي هاي ، دعني أكرر نفسي.
I don't like Lu Miaomiao.
أنا لا أحب Lu Miaomiao.
I just want to get back my sea pearl.
أريد فقط أن أستعيد لؤلؤة البحر.
Once you got your pearl back,
بمجرد أن تستعيد اللؤلؤة الخاصة بك ،
I'll find another woman for you.
سأجد لك امرأة أخرى.
At least someone like Momo.
على الأقل شخص مثل مومو.
Then I still prefer Lu Miaomiao.
ثم ما زلت أفضل لو مياومياو.
What?
ماذا؟
(The Best Homestay Voted By The Community)
(أفضل إقامة مع عائلة تم التصويت عليها من قبل المجتمع)
Sorry.
آسف.
Ms. Bai?
السيدة باي؟
What a coincidence.
يالها من صدفة.
I have something on in the homestay. I'll go back first.
لدي شيء في المنزل.  سأعود أولا.
Why is it still blue colour?
لماذا لا يزال لونه أزرق؟
♪The sign of the sea wind blown by♪
علامة ريح البحر التي تهب بها ♪
♪The footprint on the beach♪
البصمة على الشاطئ
♪You and I in the rain♪
♪ أنت وأنا في المطر ♪
♪Are so poetic♪
♪ هل شعرية جدا ♪
♪Regarding the future♪
بخصوص المستقبل
♪That we painted♪
♪ الذي رسمناه ♪
♪Every word we say♪
♪ كل كلمة نقولها ♪
♪Is surreal♪
♪ هل سريالية